<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:msxsl="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:xslt" xmlns:user="urn:dummy-scripts" xmlns:exsl="http://exslt.org/common">
  <channel>
    <title><![CDATA[Breaking News]]></title>
    <link />
    <description><![CDATA[Denver Post]]></description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 5 Sep 2012 17:15:28 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <pubDate>Wed, 5 Sep 2012 14:48:05 -0600</pubDate>
      <lastUpdated>Wed, 5 Sep 2012 16:49:16 -0600</lastUpdated>
      <title><![CDATA[Rare Colorado plague case had Girl Scout near death]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>&nbsp;Let no one say Sierra Jane Downing  has not earned her Girl Scout badge for bubonic plague.</p><p>If the 107-degree fever didn't clinch it, temporarily stumping a state-full of doctors would do. If a flight rescue and two weeks in hospital didn't clear the bar, then being named the only Colorado plague case in six years certainly would.</p><p>Sierra Jane, 7, is recovering at Rocky Mountain Hospital for Children at Presbyterian/St. Luke's, after apparently picking up the plague from flea bites on a picnic near Pagosa Springs. She was pondering the fate of a half-eaten squirrel carcass, asking her parents for a proper burial, when the fleas jumped onto a sweatshirt and bit her after she tied it around her waist.</p><p>The Downing family outing in the southwestern Colorado town morphed days later into a nightmarish medical mystery. Five days after their family picnic, Sierra Jane woke up with a high fever. By that night, she was having seizures and temperature spikes in a Pagosa Springs ER.</p><p>The Pagosa Springs doctor, sensing the girl's life was in serious danger, phoned hospitals around the state for expertise on the odd combination of symptoms. </p><p>Dr. Jennifer Snow, on call in the ICU at Rocky Mountain Children's, urged the girl's transport to Denver. Then she started hitting the books.</p><p>Septic shock. Seizures. Deathly high temperature. Swollen lymph nodes in the thigh. And then the  detailed story of outdoorsy Sierra Jane's encounter with the dead squirrel.</p><p>Snow said she went to an online database of medical journals, and within two minutes had her "ah-ha" moment from a periodical called "Chest." Teenager, same symptoms=bubonic plague.</p><p>Snow consulted with colleagues Wendi Drummond  and Tracy Butler, and immediately ordered a switch to a more specific antibiotic known to attack the plague. They also called the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, which happens to have plague experts in Colorado.</p><p> Though the disease hits only five to seven humans a year nationwide and is highly treatable when caught, the doctors were extremely worried. Even with the right antibiotic, Sierra Jane might get worse before she got better, as her body rolled through the shock of treatments.</p><p>"She was unstable. Septic shock can be fatal. These are the golden hours" of early, aggressive treatment, Snow said.</p><p>Identifying the plague also meant warnings to the hospital staff and Sierra Jane's family: wear masks, gowns and gloves at all times in the girl's room. Bubonic plague spread by animals and insects can turn into pneumonic plague when the disease is inhaled by humans.</p><p>Darcy Downing, Sierra Jane's mom, said she was actually grateful instead of terrified at word of the "plague." </p><p>"Good, we're getting an answer. Plague can be fought," she said.</p><p>Sierra Jane began to recover, and nearly two weeks after her flight for life, she may be released in a few days. She has taken short walks and sits upright in a wheelchair, but looks exhausted, and is annoyed at the two IV lines chafing her neck.</p><p>Throughout, the three Denver doctors have been waiting to encounter another doctor who has hands-on treatment of a plague patient.</p><p>But  as far as personal expertise goes, "this is it," they said, pointing to each other.</p><p>Local, state and federal officials consulted about new plague warnings for the San Juan area, but did not find an unusual animal die-off or other concerns. They posted reminders at the campground about avoiding animals and wearing bug spray, but a tiny, background level of plague in wild animals is a Colorado fact.</p><p>Darcy and Sierra Jane want to put together a Girl Scout unit on diseases in the wilderness, and how to handle animal encounters &mdash; alive or dead. Sierra Jane should make a full recovery.</p><p>In the meantime, the Downings are grateful for the Pagosa Springs doctor who sounded the alarm, and the neighbors who helped them move their house while they've been gone.</p><p>"If you ever want to see what it's supposed to be like in a small town, look at Pagosa Springs," Darcy Downing said. She said an infection is rampant there &mdash; "it's love," she said. </p><p><i>Michael Booth: 303-954-1686, <a href='mailto:mbooth@denverpost.com'>mbooth@denverpost.com</a> or <a href='http://twitter.com/mboothdp'>twitter.com/mboothdp</a></i></p><P><iframe src="http://embed.newsinc.com/Single/iframe.html?wid=2&vid=23797357&cid=507&freewheel=90115&sitesection=ttdenverpost&height=360&width=600" height='360' width='600' frameborder=no scrolling=no noresize marginwidth=0px marginheight=0px></iframe> </p>]]></description>
      <link><![CDATA[http://www.denverpost.com/news/ci_21473958]]></link>
      <media:content url="http://extras.mnginteractive.com/live/media/site36/2012/0905/20120905__plague~p1.jpg" fileSize="62497" type="image/pjpeg" />
    </item>
    <item>
      <pubDate>Wed, 5 Sep 2012 16:44:44 -0600</pubDate>
      <lastUpdated>Wed, 5 Sep 2012 16:44:53 -0600</lastUpdated>
      <title><![CDATA[Latino officers' discrimination complaints against Denver dismissed]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>A federal judge on Wednesday dismissed most of the remaining claims in a discrimination lawsuit originally filed in 2008 by Latino cops against the City of Denver and its police department. </p><p>U.S. District Court Judge R. Brooke Jackson granted the city summary judgement against the claims of seven of eight current or former officers who alleged the department engaged in systemic racial and gender employment discrimination. </p><p>"Obviously, they are disappointed with the decision but they believe that as the result of them standing up for what they believe was right there have been some changes," said Leonard Martinez, lawyer for the plaintiffs. </p><p>City Attorney Douglas Friednash declined to comment on the order, saying the claims of one officer, Det. Daniel Rojas, must still be tried. </p><p>The judge said  Rojas established there was cause to hear his case, and a trial is scheduled to begin next Wednesday in U.S. District Court in Denver. </p><p>Rojas was suspended for  meeting with informants without first telling a supervisor and without another officer to witness the meeting. </p><p>However, he claimed that he was given a desk assignment during the resulting internal affairs investigation and kept in that position after he should have been returned to normal duty. </p><p>Rojas said the work assignment was punitive and cost him overtime and financial incentives. "Detective Rojas claims this assignment continued four months after all significant charges had been dismissed," the complaint says.</p><p>The judge found that "because Detective Rojas remained on desk duty when it seems he should have been relieved, the action of keeping him on desk duty constitutes its own adverse employment action."</p><p>But in seven other cases the judge found the plaintiffs failed to establish evidence of discrimination or that the city had provided legitimate, non-discriminatory reasons for actions that ranged from termination to refusing a promotion. </p><p>Sixteen police plaintiffs filed the original suit on July 16, 2008, requesting that it be heard as a class action. </p><p> Two years later, U.S. District Judge Philip Brimmer denied the motion to certify a class of current and former Latino officers &mdash;  going back to 1979 &mdash;  because the officers were unable to prove that their gender and racial discrimination claims had a common link under the law.</p><p>The officers said  they were denied employment and promotions, were unfairly disciplined and were retaliated against when they complained to superiors about discrimination.</p><p><i>Tom McGhee: 303-954-1671, <a href='mailto:tmcghee@denverpost.com'>tmcghee@denverpost.com</a> or <a href='http://twitter.com/dpmcghee'>twitter.com/dpmcghee</a></i></p>]]></description>
      <link><![CDATA[http://www.denverpost.com/news/ci_21475123]]></link>
      <media:content url="" fileSize="" type="" />
    </item>
    <item>
      <pubDate>Wed, 5 Sep 2012 16:29:16 -0600</pubDate>
      <lastUpdated>Wed, 5 Sep 2012 16:36:09 -0600</lastUpdated>
      <title><![CDATA[Diana DeGette slams Romney-Ryan ticket, says they would make women "second-class"]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>CHARLOTTE&nbsp;&mdash;&nbsp; U.S. Rep. Diana DeGette offered up a late-afternoon broadside against what Democrats say is the "war on women" being waged by their Republican rivals.</p><p>The longtime Denver congresswoman argued at her party's national convention here Wednesday that Republican Mitt Romney would be a poor choice for women as president, saying that  he and his running mate, Wisconsin Rep. Paul Ryan, support policies that are harmful to this critical demographic.</p><p>"With proposal, after proposal Mitt Romney and Paul Ryan want to make women second-class citizens again," DeGette said.</p><p>Women will play an out-sized role in deciding the presidential contest and so Democrats and Republicans both are vying for female voters in key states like Colorado.
</p><p>"Mr. Romney, Mr. Ryan, the women of America have a message for you," DeGette said. "We're not going back. We're going forward. Forward with a president who understands and defends the rights and interests of American women."</p><p>Colorado Republicans were quick to respond.</p><p>"The only thing Barack Obama continues to move forward is more crippling debt, which has reached a record $16 trillion," said state GOP spokesman Chuck Poplstein. "Diana DeGette can try and paint the race in divisive social issues, but the reality is, with Barack Obama at the helm the economy continues to sink."</p><p><i>Chuck Plunkett: 303-954-1333, <a href='mailto:cplunkett@denverpost.com'>cplunkett@denverpost.com</a> or <a href='http://twitter.com/chuckplunkett'>twitter.com/chuckplunkett</a></i></p>]]></description>
      <link><![CDATA[http://www.denverpost.com/news/ci_21475058]]></link>
      <media:content url="" fileSize="" type="" />
    </item>
    <item>
      <pubDate>Wed, 5 Sep 2012 15:17:58 -0600</pubDate>
      <lastUpdated>Wed, 5 Sep 2012 16:36:07 -0600</lastUpdated>
      <title><![CDATA[Man who allegedly kicked, stomped puppy facing felony animal cruelty charge ]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[The 26-year-old man arrested last week after witnesses say he kicked and stomped a 4-month-old puppy made his first appearance in a Boulder courtroom this afternoon. He was formally charged with aggravated cruelty to animals and one count of obstructing a peace officer. <br /><br />Edward McMorris was arrested on Aug. 29 after witnesses began calling Boulder police just after 11:45 p.m. to report a man was kicking and stomping on a dog's head near the intersection of Canyon Boulevard and Broadway, according to a police report. When officers arrived on scene they saw a man, later identified as McMorris, dragging a "listless and hardly responsive" puppy by a leash behind him, according to the report. <br /><br />McMorris refused to give police the dog or comply with officer commands. <span id="Global_Site">One officer noticed a large metal object hanging from McMorris' belt and tackled him to the ground when McMorris reached for it.</span><br /><br />The puppy, which McMorris said was named Tater, was taken to the Boulder Emergency Vet Clinic and kept overnight after the incident. He has since been transferred to Humane Society of Boulder Valley, where he continues to recover from injuries while being monitored by veterinarians, according to Boulder police. <br /><br />No one is being allowed to adopt Tater while the case against McMorris remains open, according to the humane society.<br /><br />Deputy District Attorney Jenny McClintock will be handling the case on behalf of the Boulder District Attorney's Office. McClintock is specially trained to handle animal cruelty cases.<br /><br />Aggravated cruelty to animals is a Class 6 felony that carries a sentencing range of one year to 18 months in prison, while obstructing a peace officer is a Class 2 misdemeanor that carries a maximum penalty of one year in jail in the event of a conviction. <br /><br />McMorris, who appeared in custody Wednesday afternoon, is next scheduled to appear in court for a preliminary hearing on Sept. 27 at 1:30 p.m. <br /><br /><br /><br /><br /><br />&nbsp;<br /><br /><br /><br /><br /><br /><br /><br /><br /><br /><br /><br /><br /><br />]]></description>
      <link><![CDATA[http://www.denverpost.com/news/ci_21474226]]></link>
      <media:content url="http://extras.mnginteractive.com/live/media/site21/2012/0905/20120905_043530_Edward McMorris73.jpg" fileSize="1980310" type="image/pjpeg" />
    </item>
    <item>
      <pubDate>Wed, 5 Sep 2012 15:21:21 -0600</pubDate>
      <lastUpdated>Wed, 5 Sep 2012 15:22:24 -0600</lastUpdated>
      <title><![CDATA[Jefferson County deputies hunt for assailant dressed in Goth attire]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>A search is underway for a person dressed it what is described as Goth attire, who forced his way into a Jefferson County condo and stabbed a woman.</p><p>The assault happened about 2 p.m. at a condominium complex at 6764 S. Webster St. near Littleton, said Sheriff's Department spokeswoman Jacki Kelley. </p><p>The man, who was white and appeared to be in his 20s, was "dressed in all black," she said, including a  black cap and black eye liner. The woman suffered a stab wound, but it is not life-threatening, Kelley said.</p><p>"We're not sure about the relationship between the two, or even if there was one," she said.</p><p>The man ran away after the attack, which so far is being characterized as an attempted robbery.</p><p>Several schools nearby were put on lockdown briefly, Kelley said, "just to make sure he didn't try to escape into one of our schools."</p><p>Anyone with information or who sees the man should call 911, Kelley said.</p>]]></description>
      <link><![CDATA[http://www.denverpost.com/news/ci_21474317]]></link>
      <media:content url="" fileSize="" type="" />
    </item>
    <item>
      <pubDate>Wed, 5 Sep 2012 10:52:36 -0600</pubDate>
      <lastUpdated>Wed, 5 Sep 2012 14:48:13 -0600</lastUpdated>
      <title><![CDATA[Serial groper in Denver allegedly fondles fourth woman]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>A fourth woman was fondled near Washington Park on Tuesday  in the latest attack by what appears to be a serial groper.</p><p>Around 12:20 p.m. the  woman was walking toward the park on Kentucky Avenue, between Gilpin and Franklin streets, when she passed a man standing in the alley, according to Denver police. After she passed, the man allegedly approached her from behind and fondled her.</p><p>The suspect, who was described as being in his early 30s, heavy-set, bald and wearing a white T-shirt, sped off in what appeared to be a black or dark colored Nissan Altima or a four-door Maxima.</p><p> <a href="http://www.denverpost.com/breakingnews/ci_21428326" target="_top">A similar suspect was involved in an alleged groping </a>on Aug. 21. Around 2:30 p.m., a  woman was fondled while she was walking near Fifth Avenue and High Street. A few minutes later a second woman was walking just a block away when a suspect matching the description of the first man grabbed her buttock and fled in a dark car.</p><p>Both women told police that the man parked in an alley and waited from them to walk by.</p><p>Around 7 p.m. on Aug. 28, a woman was approached by a man matching the suspect's description near Osceola  and West 37th streets. The man allegedly grabbed the woman's backside and fled.</p><p>A $2,000 reward is being offered for information that leads to the suspects arrest. Anyone with information is asked to call Crime Stoppers at 720-913-7867.</p>]]></description>
      <link><![CDATA[http://www.denverpost.com/news/ci_21472563]]></link>
      <media:content url="" fileSize="" type="" />
    </item>
    <item>
      <pubDate>Wed, 5 Sep 2012 13:49:17 -0600</pubDate>
      <lastUpdated>Wed, 5 Sep 2012 14:42:08 -0600</lastUpdated>
      <title><![CDATA[Baby-sitter arrested on sexual assault charges in Lone Tree]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>A 22-year-old woman accused of sexually assaulting a child in her care was arrested in Lone Tree on Friday.</p><p>Chantella Lucero was baby-sitting the child when the alleged assault occurred.</p><p>She was arrested on suspicion of sexual assault on a child and sexual assault by one in a position of trust, according to a news release from the Lone Tree Police Department.</p><p>Lucero was booked into the Douglas County Jail.</p><p>The investigation is ongoing.</p>]]></description>
      <link><![CDATA[http://www.denverpost.com/news/ci_21473689]]></link>
      <media:content url="http://extras.mnginteractive.com/live/media/site36/2012/0905/20120905__luceroMUG~p1.jpg" fileSize="35879" type="image/pjpeg" />
    </item>
    <item>
      <pubDate>Tue, 4 Sep 2012 16:44:49 -0600</pubDate>
      <lastUpdated>Wed, 5 Sep 2012 13:38:53 -0600</lastUpdated>
      <title><![CDATA[Libby Weaver departing Fox31 after nearly 13 years as anchor]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Libby Weaver, co-anchor at KDVR-Fox31 for almost 13 years, will leave the station at the end of the year or early in 2013. </p><p>Weaver has been half of the longest-lasting late news anchor team in Denver TV, along with Ron Zappolo, who previously announced his intention to step down.</p><p> <a href="http://kdvr.com/author/kdvrlibbyweaver/" target="_blank">Weaver</a> who teamed for the 5 and 9 p.m. newscasts with veteran Denver anchor  Zappolo, and has recently  been co-anchor with Jeremy Hubbard on the early evening and late  night newscasts, was not available for comment Tuesday. The station confirmed her departure without specifying the reason. </p><p>"We can confirm that Libby Weaver will be leaving KDVR sometime around the end of this year or early in January," according to News Director Ed Kosowski. "Beyond that we cannot and will not discuss anything else at this time about Libby's departure except to say that we will certainly miss her presence both on the air in our newscasts and in the newsroom."</p><p> <a href="http://www.denverpost.com/dustysaunders/ci_19329776" target="_blank"> Zappolo</a> has previously announced his intention to step down as news anchor and return to sports coverage in March 2013 when his contract expires. This summer he marked  <a href="http://kdvr.com/2012/08/01/fox31s-ron-zappolo-celebrates-35-years-of-broadcasting-in-denver/" target="_blank">35 years in Denver broadcasting</a>. </p><p>The end of the Weaver-Zappolo run presents an unusual dilemma/opportunity for KDVR management, which has been talking to Weaver for months; the newsroom has been buzzing about the plan for weeks.</p><p>Weaver joined Fox31 in July 2000 after serving as the host of the syndicated "EXTRA" in Los Angeles and working for WMAQ in Chicago. </p><p>Kosowski on Tuesday declined to specify or speculate on future assignments. However, Hubbard, who  returned to Colorado from ABC News in New York in 2011 to anchor  FOX31's "Nightside" and sister station KWGN's "News at 7," is poised to take over prominent anchor duties. He previously worked at KDVR from 2004-2007 and has long been the  heir apparent to Zappolo's side of the anchor desk. </p><p>The station expects to make a more detailed announcement in coming weeks but plans no immediate  decision on Weaver's successor.</p><p><i>Joanne Ostrow: 303-954-1830, jostrow@denverpost.com or twitter.com/ostrowdp</i></p>]]></description>
      <link><![CDATA[http://www.denverpost.com/news/ci_21467181]]></link>
      <media:content url="http://extras.mnginteractive.com/live/media/site36/2012/0904/20120904__AE04TVWEAVER~p1.jpg" fileSize="9311" type="image/pjpeg" />
    </item>
    <item>
      <pubDate>Wed, 5 Sep 2012 13:02:36 -0600</pubDate>
      <lastUpdated>Wed, 5 Sep 2012 13:06:00 -0600</lastUpdated>
      <title><![CDATA[Auction of art (and rhubarb pie) fills Rist Canyon VFD account with $110,000]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>RIST CANYON&nbsp;&mdash;&nbsp;The Richard Schmid Fine Art Auction poured $110,000 into Rist Canyon Volunteer Fire Department accounts Sunday, up from the $40,000 collected last year, auction organizer and firefighter Wes Rutt said.</p><p>Rist Canyon VFD, which fought the High Park fire west of Fort Collins for three weeks in June, collects no taxes and so counts heavily on the fine-art auction to boost its operating budget.</p><p>Typically, artists donate 40 percent of their sales to the fire department. This year, many donated 100 percent, Rutt said.</p><p>The High Park fire burned  one of Rist Canyon VFD's stations and several firefighters were among those who lost homes in the 87,284-acre blaze that destroyed 259 houses and cabins and killed one person.</p><p>Barb  Monesson and her firefighter husband, Larry, were among those who found themselves sifting through the ruins of a burned home in the Whale Rock neighborhood. All that was left behind were pieces of Larry's woodcarvings and the hints of a rhubarb plant. In the weeks that followed, the couple carried bottled water to the plant and nurtured it until it produced enough stalks to make a pie.</p><p>That pie, made by Barb Monesson, sold to Jon Stephens for $1,000 during the auction.</p><p>Stephens, who lives in the Stove Prairie neighborhood, said Sunday he stuck through the fierce bidding for the pretty-as-a-picture pie &mdash; with plastic knife and fork included &mdash; because  "the fire department works hard. I wanted to help."</p><p>The auction is held the Sunday of Labor Day weekend each year, in conjunction with the Rist Canyon Mountain Festival.</p>]]></description>
      <link><![CDATA[http://www.denverpost.com/news/ci_21473277]]></link>
      <media:content url="http://extras.mnginteractive.com/live/media/site36/2012/0904/20120904__auction_pie1~p1.jpg" fileSize="38896" type="image/pjpeg" />
    </item>
    <item>
      <pubDate>Wed, 5 Sep 2012 12:46:34 -0600</pubDate>
      <lastUpdated>Wed, 5 Sep 2012 12:52:49 -0600</lastUpdated>
      <title><![CDATA[Greeley school ban on gang numbers includes Peyton Manning's 18]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>GREELEY TRIBUNE&nbsp;&mdash;&nbsp;Christopher Cox is behind bars for the next 42 years for his part in Weld County's first successful gang-related organized crime prosecution. </p><p>Cox was an 18th Street gang member. So when Greeley-Evans School District 6 says students can not wear sports jerseys or any attire with the number 18 on it, it's no offense to Peyton Manning. The district just wants to keep its students safe, officials say. </p><p>"We take a very hard stance against gang attire," said Roger Fiedler, the district's director of communications. "We want to keep it off our school grounds." </p><p>The dress code has been in effect for several years now, but when a third-grader from Monfort Elementary was recently sent home to change out of his Denver Bronco Manning jersey, it was thrown back into the spotlight.</p><p>Read the rest of this report at  <a href="http://www.greeleytribune.com/news/2453316-113/gang-district-manning-street" target="_top">GreeleyTribune.com</a></p>]]></description>
      <link><![CDATA[http://www.denverpost.com/news/ci_21473182]]></link>
      <media:content url="http://extras.mnginteractive.com/live/media/site36/2012/0902/20120902_030756_thing-pmanning-jfox-broncos.jpg" fileSize="0" type="image/jpeg" />
    </item>
    <item>
      <pubDate>Wed, 5 Sep 2012 12:32:04 -0600</pubDate>
      <lastUpdated>Wed, 5 Sep 2012 12:37:24 -0600</lastUpdated>
      <title><![CDATA[Police standoff ends after 2nd day in Pagosa Springs]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Police have a man in custody after a standoff lasted more than a day, prompting the Archuleta County School District to cancel classes Wednesday. </p><p>Police say Tuesday morning at 9 a.m. an officer stopped a Dodge Caravan for a traffic stop, when they say the man driving began yelling at the officer and pulled a handgun.</p><p>The officer called for backup, and officers from the police, Archuleta County Sheriff's Department and the State Patrol responded. </p><p>The driver had been barricaded in his vehicle ever since. Police said he was making suicidal threats. </p><p>Get more news at  <a href="http://www.9news.com/news/article/287355/339/Standoff-in-second-day-in-Pagosa-Springs" target="_top">9News.com</a></p>]]></description>
      <link><![CDATA[http://www.denverpost.com/news/ci_21473101]]></link>
      <media:content url="http://extras.mnginteractive.com/live/media/site36/2012/0905/20120905__PagosaStandoff~p1.jpg" fileSize="25457" type="image/pjpeg" />
    </item>
    <item>
      <pubDate>Wed, 5 Sep 2012 12:12:08 -0600</pubDate>
      <lastUpdated>Wed, 5 Sep 2012 12:14:51 -0600</lastUpdated>
      <title><![CDATA[Paul Ryan holds rally in Colorado Springs on Thursday]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>COLORADO SPRINGS&nbsp;&mdash;&nbsp;Republican vice presidential candidate Paul Ryan will be in Colorado Springs on Thursday morning for a rally, according to a campaign news release.</p><p>Doors open at WestPac Restorations, at 765 Aviation Way, at 7:30 a.m. Thursday. Ryan is scheduled to speak at 10:10 a.m.</p><p>Those who want to attend must register and obtain a ticket for the event on the  <a href="http://cospringsryan.eventbrite.com/" target="_top">Romney-Ryan campaign website.</a></p><p>Get more El Paso County news at  <a href="http://www.Gazette.com" target="_top">Gazette.com</a></p>]]></description>
      <link><![CDATA[http://www.denverpost.com/news/ci_21472906]]></link>
      <media:content url="http://extras.mnginteractive.com/live/media/site36/2012/0814/20120814__CD14Ryan_DSC4721~p1.jpg" fileSize="166358" type="image/pjpeg" />
    </item>
    <item>
      <pubDate>Tue, 4 Sep 2012 19:08:57 -0600</pubDate>
      <lastUpdated>Wed, 5 Sep 2012 11:53:00 -0600</lastUpdated>
      <title><![CDATA[Families of Aurora shooting victims unveil plan for relief fund]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>In an effort to build on preliminary discussions during a meeting last week, families of victims  from the mass shooting at the Century Aurora 16 theater  revealed a 16-point plan Tuesday that  they hope will be adopted by the committee overseeing a multimillion dollar donation fund. </p><p>Victims' families and committee members from the 7/20 Recovery Fund &mdash; which is handling the estimated $5 million in donations &mdash; met  Friday after vowing  transparency in the distribution of the money.</p><p>They meet again Wednesday night, just a week after some family members harshly criticized how the recovery fund is being handled. 
</p><p>The thorough plan outlines suggestions that range from the disbursement of victim payments to the creation,  make-up and role of various sub-committees that should be involved in the process of distributing the money.</p><p>Among the key points the family members are suggesting: </p><p> &bull; The victims'  fund will include all money collected by Giving First, Community First or any of its affiliates designated for victims of the July 20 shooting, including The Aurora Victim's Relief Fund, the 7/20 Recovery funds, donations collected by the Colorado Organization for Victim Assistance and the City of Aurora. All of the money in the funds will be paid directly to the victims, including interest. If any fund's use is in doubt,  it will default to the victims' fund unless a use is proven. </p><p> &bull; 
All the money already collected and still being collected should be placed a central, coordinated fund outside of the non-profits that have received the donations. The 7/20 Recovery Committee would have access to this money.
</p><p> &bull; No money should be distributed until the Victim Resource Committee &mdash; to be made up of at least 60 percent victim family members &mdash; recommends a distribution plan  approved by the already formed executive committee.  Emergency assistance for victims in dire need should be covered quickly to prevent additional suffering. </p><p> &bull;  Encourage health-care providers to forgive the difference between the cost of care and the amount covered by insurance and assure that victims are not responsible for co-pays, the cost of medication and any physical therapy or required medical devices.</p><p>"At least they're actually soliciting input from us,"  Tom Teves said Tuesday. He is  the father of Alex Teves, who was one of 12 killed when a gunman opened fire on a midnight showing of "The Dark Knight Rises." Fifty-eight others were injured in the July 20 attack.
</p><p>Teves said the  "actions" of the 7/20 Recovery Committee will show whether its members are listening. </p><p>Unlike the Friday meeting,  where only family members of deceased victims were in attendance, Wednesday's meeting will be open to all of those who were injured .  </p><p><i>Kurtis Lee: 303-954-1655, <a href='mailto:klee@denverpost.com'>klee@denverpost.com</a> or <a href='http://twitter.com/kurtisalee'>twitter.com/kurtisalee</a></i></p>]]></description>
      <link><![CDATA[http://www.denverpost.com/news/ci_21468240]]></link>
      <media:content url="" fileSize="" type="" />
    </item>
    <item>
      <pubDate>Wed, 5 Sep 2012 11:42:16 -0600</pubDate>
      <lastUpdated>Wed, 5 Sep 2012 11:46:55 -0600</lastUpdated>
      <title><![CDATA[Frozen cow catastrophe marks end of Conundrum cabin near Aspen]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>ASPEN&nbsp;&mdash;&nbsp;It's unlikely there will be people partying or cows dying in the old cabin near Conundrum Hot Springs any longer.</p><p>The U.S. Forest Service removed the tin roof from the structure over the course of the summer and recently finished the job, according to Andrew Larson, lead wilderness ranger in the Aspen-Sopris District. For now, the plan is to allow the wooden frame of the cabin to deteriorate in the harsh weather at 11,200 feet in elevation.</p><p>The  <a href="http://www.denverpost.com/breakingnews/ci_20467888" target="_top">cabin gained notoriety last winter when it was discovered that six cows froze to death inside </a>after apparently seeking shelter during a snowstorm. The cows were among 29 that wandered into the Conundrum Valley from the Crested Butte side of the Continental Divide.</p><p>Read the rest of this report at  <a href="http://www.aspentimes.com/article/20120905/NEWS/120909935" target="_top">AspenTimes.com</a></p>]]></description>
      <link><![CDATA[http://www.denverpost.com/news/ci_21472759]]></link>
      <media:content url="http://extras.mnginteractive.com/live/media/site36/2012/0424/20120424__CowCabin~p1.jpg" fileSize="42259" type="image/pjpeg" />
    </item>
    <item>
      <pubDate>Wed, 5 Sep 2012 10:57:44 -0600</pubDate>
      <lastUpdated>Wed, 5 Sep 2012 10:58:42 -0600</lastUpdated>
      <title><![CDATA[22-year-old motorcyclist killed in head-on crash in Park County]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>A head-on crash between a motorcycle and car killed a 22-year-old man in Park County on Monday.</p><p>Around 9:45 p.m., Kyle Rosenwinge was driving his 1999 Yamaha motorcycle southbound on U.S. Highway 285 when drifted into the northbound lane as he rounded a right-hand curve, said Trooper Nate Reid, a spokesman for the Colorado State Patrol.</p><p>Rosenwinge, of Bailey, collided head-on with a 2005 red Subaru Outback traveling northbound.</p><p>Rosenwinge died at the scene. The driver and passenger in the Subaru were not injured.</p><p>Authorities suspect Rosenwinge may have been drinking before the crash. Toxicology test are being completed.</p><p><i>Jordan Steffen: 303-954-1794, <a href='mailto:jsteffen@denverpost.com'>jsteffen@denverpost.com</a> or <a href='http://twitter.com/jsteffendp'>twitter.com/jsteffendp</a></i></p>]]></description>
      <link><![CDATA[http://www.denverpost.com/news/ci_21472586]]></link>
      <media:content url="" fileSize="" type="" />
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>